[{
        "question": "7 + (-13)",
        "answer": "-6"
    },
    {
        "question": "-9 + (-3)",
        "answer": "-12"
    },
    {
        "question": "100 + 5",
        "answer": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "35 - (-5)",
        "answer": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 50",
        "answer": "-41"
    },
    {
        "question": "26 - 9 + (-17)",
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "-46 + 46",
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "100 + (-500)",
        "answer": "-400"
    },
    {
        "question": "-9 - (-5) + 6",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 42 - 9",
        "answer": "-37"
    },
    {
        "question": "-6 + 2 - (-16)",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "50 - 23 + (-7)",
        "answer": "20"
    }

]